{
"question": "夕方",
"answer": "ゆうがた"
},
{
"question": "低い",
"answer": "ひくい"
},
{
"question": "左",
"answer": "ひだり"
},
{
"question": "毎週",
"answer": "まいしゅう"
},
{
"question": "下手-2",
"answer": "へた"
},
{
"question": "千",
"answer": "せん"
},
{
"question": "渡す",
"answer": "わたす"
},
{
"question": "午前",
"answer": "ごぜん"
},
{
"question": "丸い",
"answer": "まるい"
},
{
"question": "便利",
"answer": "べんり"
},
{
"question": "今月",
"answer": "こんげつ"
},
{
"question": "浴びる",
"answer": "あびる"
},
{
"question": "半",
"answer": "はん"
},
{
"question": "洋服",
"answer": "ようふく"
},
{
"question": "撮る",
"answer": "とる"
},
{
"question": "締める",
"answer": "しめる"
},
{
"question": "文章",
"answer": "ぶんしょう"
},
{
"question": "薄い",
"answer": "うすい"
},
{
"question": "八",
"answer": "はち"
},
{
"question": "横",
"answer": "よこ"
},
